SHEELA MYSORE

O A A N A L Y S T



5 5142481503

Sheelamanohar.03@gmail.com



PROFILE

Dedicated Software Professional bringing more than 18 years of experience and diligence to handle needs of large and complex products. Solid history in COBOL development, manual testing and a developing automated tester. Seek to apply expertise to growth-oriented, dynamic position.

SKILLS

- Postman, Swagger, BDD
- · Git, JIRA, Confluence
- Selenium
- Basics in Python and Java
- COBOL development, SQL
- MS 365 Products
- Undergoing Salesforce admin training
- Basics in Tableau

EXPERIENCE

QA ANALYST

ADD SYSTEMS

Mar 2022 - Dec 2022

- Create manual test-cases and automation scripts for products under test
- Timely automate functional and regression level test cases
- Execute test cases
- Create automation scripts using Test Complete, Python, BDD

QA AUTOMATION ANALYST

J.D. Power

Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

- Knowledge of Software development life cycle
- Create manual test-cases and automation scripts for products under test
- Timely automate functional and regression level test cases
- Create and execute automation test cases
- Execute regression testing and analyze the results to provide recommendations
- Work with cross functional project teams
- Testing of various ETL, MS and business services using Postman, Swagger.
- Updating automation scripts based on BDD (Cucumber feature files, Java).
- Version control tool Gitlab.
- IDE-IntelliJ, Eclipse.
- Defect Tracking tool JIRA.
- Training completed on Selenium.
- Execute SQL queries to validate data

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

National Institute of Engineering, India

Major in Electrical and Electronics

1998-2002

QA Analyst

Fresche Solutions Inc

Dec 2019-Aug 2021

- Responsibilities included QA testing, raising defects, co-ordinating with development team, test documents
 preparation, attending stake holders meeting, co-ordinating with the customer, communication and status
 reporting.
- The application was based on a AS400 system which involved manual testing.

Developer

Fresche Solutions Inc April 2014 - Dec 2019

• Technologies worked on - RPGLE, COBOL, DB2 - SQL

Tech Lead

Software Paradigms Inc July 2011 - Dec 2013

- Technologies worked on COBOL, JCL, DB2 SQL, basics in UNIX
- Team lead (team size 8 to 10 people). Coordination with onsite counterpart, gathering requirements, assigning tasks, reviews and tracking the tasks to closure

Associate Consultant

Mindtree

July 2007 - July 2011

• Technologies worked on - COBOL, JCL, DB2 - SQL

Developer

Infosys Ltd

Aug 2003 - Jun 2007

• Technologies worked on - COBOL, JCL, DB2 - SQL, QTP

Professional Development:

Completed the following online courses @ LinkedIn learning. Keen to learn new tools and technologies and scale up to the demands of the project.

Learning Jira Software
Test Automation Foundations
Selenium Essential Training
Python automation and Testing
HTML Essential Training